Wow.
- That was exhausting.
- That was something, huh?
- Good ride, Boyd, good ride.
- Oh, look at that!
- Oh, man.
- That is gorgeous.
It's beautiful.
- Well done, huh?
- Let's get a picture of the group.
You know what?
That's great idea.
- Um...
- Where do you wanna...
- Right there. I think...
- Right here on the rock?
- Right there.
- Now come over here.
- Come on, everybody, let's line up.
- All right, line it up.
Get tight, and we'll get
back on the road and ride some more.
- All right, you ready?
- How's my hair?
- All right.
- Okay, one more.
- Got it. One more vertical.
- How's my hair look?
All right.
Get out of the way!
What was that?
- I didn't see anybody.
- Anybody moving down there?
- That was...
- That was crazy!
- He came out of nowhere.
- Right, did you see...
Oh, my God!
Somebody get help!
- Who is this?
- Call 911!
911! Okay. I got it! I got it!
I'm getting my phone!
Help me.
- Relax.
- Help me.
It's gonna be fine.
You're gonna be okay.
It's alright.
Hang in there.
I have a question.
Theoretically, if you wanted to break
into a maximum security prison
how would you do it?
You mean to get past
the razor wire perimeter fence
the roaming patrols
closed-circuit camera surveillance?
Yes.
Theoretically, I don't think you can break
into a maximum security prison.
Hmm. Hmm.
I have plenty of other things
I could be doing, Lisbon.
I don't know why you
brought me out here.
It's good to get
out in the sunshine and the fresh air.
You've been holed up for weeks
obsessing over Lorelei Martins.
It's unhealthy.
Lorelei Martins is the closest
we've ever gotten to Red John.
It doesn't bother you that the FBI
just took her away from us?
Of course it bothers me
but there's nothing I can do about it.
- There's nothing you can do, either.
- How long is this gonna take?
It's a jurisdictional thing.
It shouldn't take more than a couple hours.
- Jurisdictional?
- Vehicular fatality. We're in a state park.
Park rangers aren't equipped
to deal with this sort of thing.
That's why we're here...
to do the paperwork.
Excellent. Let's get on with it.
Shall we?
You guys must be CBI.
It's about time. Sign here.
All right.
- Just my luck. Damn it!
- What?
Get your yellow tape out.
It's a crime scene.
Say what?
It's a murder. Do whatever it is
you do when it's a murder.
Murder? What?
No, it... it was an accident.
Oh, really?
Why weren't there any skid marks?
- Well, but...
- Damage to the guard rail
indicates the car went straight
through it at a high rate of speed.
Which means the driver
never engaged the brakes
never touched
the steering wheel.
So then it's a suicide.
She was halfway
through a cheeseburger.
She just had her car cleaned.
And where's her handbag?
A woman like this would have a handbag
unless, of course, you have it.
Do you have her handbag?
- No.
- Then it was stolen.
Probably by the same person
that pushed her off the road
or tampered with her brakes.
- Wow.
- Yes. Wow.
My work is done here.
Forensics just confirmed it.
No way those brake lines
failed on their own.
- Definitely murder.
- Poor kid.
- What have we got so far?
- Uh, the victim was Cassie Flood, 26.
She worked for Channel 7
doing human interest stories.
I recognize her.
She did that story about the baby tiger
at the zoo, right?
Probably. The last story she did was
on space travel for rich people.
"And ordinary people like me will
be able to fly into space on this"
"just walk up and buy a ticket?"
"There are no ordinary people, Cassie."
"We are all of us
extraordinary in our own way."
"How much is it gonna cost
for me to get on this flight?"
"First flight quarter of a million."
"Thereabouts."
"Wow, that is quite an expense
for a 60-minute flight."
"It's not the flight you pay for."
- "It's the landing."
- "Oh. Wow. There you have it."
- "Now back to Ed Hunt..."
- Okay. Well, she's very telegenic.
She ever do any hard news? Something
that would have made her enemies?
Yeah, maybe. Couple months ago, she did
a piece on the Bells Glen Speedway.
Started as a human interest
story about stock cars
but ended up exposing a black market
of stolen cars and auto parts.
This guy, Dickie Yuntz
set to be indicted any day.
- You and Cho follow up.
- Okay.
Grace, this was originally
treated as an accident.
Re-interview all the witnesses
from the accident report.
See if anyone remembers
anything suspicious.
Will do, boss.
Lisbon. So it's murder, is it?
It is. Let's go to the news
station the victim worked at.
Uh, I'm kind of busy.
Maybe later.
That's not how it works.
We have to do our jobs.
Well, I think you can do it.
You're very capable.
I'm not kidding.
Come on, let's go.
Okay, I'll go
to the news station with you
get you started, and then
you're on your own, all right?
I am not in the sixth grade.
That doesn't work on me.
I can't promise I'll always
be around to help you, Teresa.
All right? There will come a time when
you might have to do all this on your own
and I want you to be prepared.
I am prepared to punch you
in the face all on my own.
"And that's the weather. Ed?"
"Next up... did the vice president
really say that?"
"Right after the break."
Okay, cue up the Veep gaffe
for when we're back.
And...
Get ready to go to sports.
So, Mr. Kasmir
did Cassie ever have any
threats directed against her?
Maybe after the Bells Glen
Speedway story?
Uh, the first note came
a week ago
saying Cassie should
leave town and not come back.
The second note arrived yesterday.
Uh, you didn't think this was
worth mentioning to the police?
Look, we get crank letters
all the time.
We don't call the cops
every time one comes in.
Go with this version.
Cassie was a valued person here.
She was a part of this team.
We cared about her.
So don't mistake our commitment
to the news for a lack of feeling.
Oh, we're not here to judge.
I promise you.
We're just trying to find
Cassie's killer, same as you.
You guys are great.
Oh, tough, uh, good-looking, sincere.
Let's put you on the air
ask the public for information
- you know, blah, blah, blah.
- That's not how we work.
It could be good
for your investigation.
Maybe later, if things
don't work out.
If you were to use one word
to sum up Cassie
- what would that word be?
- Promise.
"Promise."
- She had great promise.
- Great word.
Just the other day
I was telling her she had, uh...
the anchor chair in her future.
Look, I don't wanna force
you to do anything
but public attention is good.
Bottom line... it could
help you solve the case.
- Did you, uh, get any more of these letters?
- I'll have to check with my intern
but why don't I get you
on the air and we talk about it?
- Mm, not gonna happen.
- You sure?
Absolutely positive.
I don't belong on television.
Excuse me.
CBI. We're looking
for Richard Yuntz.
Yeah.
Over there.
Police! Stop!
Get up.
California Bureau of Investigation.
- You're under arrest.
- All right, all right. Relax!
Damn, I was just going
to take a leak!
- Changes.
- Oh. Thanks.
Where are my glasses?
Tara, did you move my glasses?
I've told you before...
- Do not touch them.
- No, Ed, I didn't touch your glasses.
Well, where are they then?
You lost them, Ed
like you always do
and then you blamed me
and now I've called for the PA
to bring you another pair like I always do.
Ooh. Thank you, Erin.
Um, could you get me some
chamomile tea for my throat?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Listen here, young woman.
I have three Emmy nominations.
I've worked with Brokaw
and Blitzer.
Show a little respect.
Regional. Three regional
Emmy nominations.
Regional.
"I'm Ed Hunt..."
Say, you're the lady from the television.
- The... the... the weather, right?
- Yes.
- Uh, Tara Skye.
- That's right, yeah.
- Is that your real name?
- Yes.
- That's very convenient.
- Um...
What, uh, what can I do for you?
Autograph?
No, no.
You probably heard about the murder.
Cassie Flood, yeah.
Ugh, isn't it terrible?
- Yeah.
- You with the cops?
Well, I'm... I'm a consultant, but, uh...
you worked with Cassie, so...
You may be able
to tell me the truth.
You know, I've... I've asked
around about her
but everyone seems to wanna
tell me just what they think they should tell
you know what I mean?
- Totally. What do you wanna know?
- Mm. Well...
If you were to describe Cassie in one word
what would that word be?
She was sleeping her way
to the top, if that helps.
Well, that's a little more than one word
but I'm intrigued. Go on.
The minute she got here
she jumped in the sack with Ed Hunt.
And lately, she started
seducing Ryan Kasmir.
But... I don't...
I don't wanna speak ill of the dead.
They don't really care.
They're dead.
Lisbon. Ah, there you are.
Uh, I found a real journalist
to tell us the story.
Tara, this is Teresa Lisbon.
She works for the California
Bureau of Investigation.
- Hi.
- Tara was just telling me
- the truth about Cassie Flood.
- Really?
The day she died
I overheard her making plans to meet
with someone in secret.
Really? Who was it?
Did she tell you where she was going
or did you hear where she was going?
No, but she was conniving
and used her sexuality
to get ahead, so, you know...
You think she was planning
to meet a secret lover?
- Yeah.
- Sly minx.
- I know, right?
- Whoa.
Everyone treated her like
this perfect little angel.
- That must have been very frustrating.
- Yeah.
I had been here for 16 months
before she even showed up
and in all that time Hunt and Kasmir
never even gave me the time of day.
But her, with her east coast
journalism degree...
I mean... they...
they were falling all over her.
There she was
worrying about journalism
while you were throwing yourself
at Hunt and Kasmir
and she is the one that
ends up with the anchor chair.
Yeah. I mean, no. I me...
what?
Hell hath no fury like a slut outflanked.
You must have felt like killing her.
- Yeah. W...
- Really?
- Wait, no! No!
- No? Ow!
How dare you?
Well, she's a definite maybe.
That should give you enough
to work with, though, don't you think?
I hope that hurt.
It did.
Tara Skye resented Cassie Flood
both romantically and professionally.
And she's got no alibi.
The producer Kasmir says
he had no romantic relationship with Cassie
and he says Tara Skye
is a backstabbing bitch.
And he's got an alibi
for the night of the murder.
What about Ed Hunt?
- No alibi.
- Hmm.
Says he was at home.
Yuntz has motive and a weak alibi
plus an understanding of cars.
What about the witnesses
from the accident site?
Did they have anything useful?
Well, they all mentioned the driver
who stopped and was the first to help
and made sure the EMTs
were called.
Everybody talked about him
but I could never find him.
I've never been able
to speak to him directly.
Did you get a description?
Thirties, balding, white guy
average height, no plate.
- I'm having a sketch done.
- We can try and get a public request.
Maybe somebody will come in.
In the meantime
I'm gonna go talk to Ed Hunt.
All right.
Hey, Lisbon. Uh, don't tell me
you've finished your case already.
"We need to go and talk
to Ed Hunt. Where are you?"
Uh, I'm not really
available at the moment
but, uh, if you leave
a message after the tone...
Cho told me you asked him
how to break into a high-security prison?
Purely theoretical. And by the way
he was no help whatsoever.
You're banging your head
against the wall.
You know, I'll be back soon
so you can catch me up on your case then.
I gotta go. Bye.
I have a meeting with a client.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to turn around, sir.
But I have an appointment.
No, sir, you do not
have an appointment.
- You don't even know my name.
- Nobody has an appointment.
This is a federal prison.
We all know this money is
well pledged, don't we, folks?
The environment, global warming...
these are good causes.
And not just from the perspective
of beachfront property values.
But our host and primary backer's
commitment to these causes is no joke.
A man I have the honor
of calling a friend...
Tommy Volker.
But he's not just about saving the planet.
There's also adventure
and, uh, plenty of the good things in life.
But most importantly
there's this, ladies and gentlemen...
A seat on the maiden flight
of the Volker Intergalactic
the hardest ticket to get
in the whole world.
Bidding starts at $200,000.
And remember, you can write this off.
Thank you.
Thanks for being here.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
Thanks for being here.
Uh, Mr. Hunt.
I'm Teresa Lisbon with the CBI.
- Could we talk?
- Yeah, sure.
Cassie was a great gal.
She was a real asset to the team.
It was a tragedy to lose her.
I was told you had a relationship with her.
I have a relationship
with all my colleagues.
But I'm... I'm guessing
that you mean something more.
Yeah, I mean something more.
Is that a common occurrence
with younger reporters
or did you pick Cassie out specially?
Tara Skye has been filling
your ear with poison, has she?
The truth is, Cassie and I
were the best of friends.
- Mm.
- But we were never exclusive.
So you don't deny the affair?
Oh, "affair"... that's...
that's an awful big word.
We had a moment.
Then we both moved on.
No hard feelings.
I wonder if Cassie Flood would
agree with that description
if she were here to answer.
Here. Look. I...
got a picture of...
us at the museum's opening
of the new Asian wing
two weeks ago.
Does that look like people
who don't get along?
- Is that Tommy Volker?
- That's right.
That was the night Cassie
convinced him to do the interview.
Oh. Uh, how well do you
know Tommy Volker?
We're old friends.
We run in the same circles. Dakar, Baja.
We both like adventure...
challenges, you know.
Could... could you introduce me?
Sure. Come on.
I got people will say you told them
you had plans to spit
on Cassie Flood's grave, Mr. Yuntz
And yet the best alibi that you can offer
is that you were at the movies...
by yourself.
What can I tell you?
I might have whacked her
if I knew what kind of story she was planning
make me look so bad.
But I didn't.
So I didn't.
No point killing her
after the fact, right, Counselor?
Indeed, no point.
Uh, Agent Rigsby...
If you believe and have evidence
that my client has committed
a crime, please charge him.
Otherwise, we're done.
Yeah. We're done.
- For now.
- Always a pleasure.
Gotta get across town.
Nice talking with you
Agent Bigsby.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
Hey. Tommy.
Got someone I want you to meet.
Agent Lisbon, Tommy Volker.
Tommy, Teresa Lisbon.
From the CBI.
Oh. Would you excuse us
for a minute?
Agent. It's a pleasure.
What brings you here?
I'm looking into the death
of a young journalist, Cassie Flood.
- She interviewed you.
- Uh, excuse me.
Yeah. I heard about that. It's, uh...
it's a terrible thing. How can I help?
Does anything come to mind that might
be useful for our investigation?
She was, uh, poised
and charming for her age.
And she had a wicked sense of humor
as well. I doubt that helps much.
What a senseless tragedy.
I'm sorry. Mr. Volker, we have to go.
You're being conferenced into the
Mumbai board meeting in 20 minutes.
So sorry about this, Agent Lisbon.
If there's anything I can do
to help your investigation, I will. Um...
Uh, here's my personal number.
Call me anytime.
- And I mean that.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Yuntz lawyered up?
- Yep. We're getting nowhere.
Or maybe not.
Look at this.
The Tide's Edge hotel. Huh.
The only access is
from the road that Cassie was on.
Not only that, Cassie Flood rented
a room on her credit card.
When I called, front desk told me
Mr. Flood is still there.
- She's single.
- Nice. I'll get Cho. We'll go pick him up.
No need. CHP's bringing him in.
Should be here any minute.
This is an outrage!
Since when is California
a paramilitary state, huh?
Ow! You're hurting me!
Hey.
Are you planning on coming
to work anytime soon?
Well, yeah. Soonish.
But, uh...
Oop.
I still got a few things
to, uh, figure out.
Why, is there a break
in the case?
- As a matter of fact, there is.
- Really? What?
I've got somebody here who says Cassie Flood
was murdered by Tommy Volker.
Mr. Berman.
You may take a seat.
Or should I call you "Mr. Flood"?
All right, look.
Cassie Flood was gonna publish
a takedown piece in my magazine
showing billionaire philanthropist
Tommy Volker
to be a sleazy criminal
who just talks a good game.
And Cassie Flood brought her story
to you why?
Because of the wide readership
you receive?
Cassie and I went to journalism
school together.
And she knew that I publish a highly
respected investigative monthly.
Opinions differ.
Some think you publish a lefty rag
that sees conspiracies under every rock.
I won a Polk award.
Yeah. And you were sued for libel.
Any good journalist gets sued.
It's part of the job.
Cassie came to me because
she knew I'd have the courage
to run her story
when nobody else would.
Which was?
Volker had a geothermal project
in the Amazon rain forest
which was going to double
his presence in the emerging markets.
But when an indigenous tribe
claimed the land sacred
it threatened to kill his deal.
So he made them disappear.
- The whole tribe?
- A whole village found in a mass grave.
The killing was blamed on fighting between
drug traffickers and leftist rebels
a terrible tragedy that just so happened
to remove all opposition to Volker's project.
Oh, come on. Nobody could get
away with something like that.
Volker did.
Look, he's smart.
Does anything possible
to keep his hands clean.
He'll get other people
to do his dirty work.
- But Cassie... she caught him anyway.
- How?
She had an inside source
in Volker's organization.
That source gave her
audit trails.
Audit trails never lie.
Cassie was bringing me
the hard evidence when she died.
Audit trails?
You follow the money
you always get to the truth.
Cassie was a top-notch
investigative journalist.
She was wasted on television.
Hence the missing bag.
Grace's good Samaritan
was there to get the evidence.
Show Volker this sketch
and watch his face.
- I know what to do.
- I know you do.
You go, girl. Huh?
Thank you.
Agent Lisbon. Is there something
wrong? What's the matter?
I'm sorry to blind-side you
but I have some questions I need to ask you
if you don't mind.
- Mr. Volker's flying to New York.
- Of course.
As I said before
whatever I can do to help.
The thing is, we found out
where Cassie was going the day she died.
Really? Where?
She was going to meet a man
named Steve Berman.
- And you think this Berman killed her?
- We don't know
but he told us some pretty strange things
I wanted to run by you.
All right.
Did Cassie ever ask you
about the Amazon rain forest
- when you and she spoke?
- The Amazon rain forest? No.
Did she ever mention a geothermal project
that you have down there?
Good Lord, no.
Cassie and I talked about my...
self-consciousness
growing up with a stutter
and my feeling that I needed
to give something back
because of all I received.
That's all?
No, we also bonded over having both
been raised by our grandmothers
and we also swore
that we'd both remain committed
to making the world a better place
for our having been in it.
Amanda, you were there.
Did, uh, did our
Amazon project come up?
No. The... the Amazon
was never mentioned.
She never mentioned
a village being massacred?
Good Lord, no.
What a bizarre question.
What village? What massacre?
I'm just following a lead, sir.
You know, perhaps I should
give you an alibi.
It's all right. I wouldn't expect a man in
your position to do the dirty work himself.
I'm sorry.
No offense. Cop humor.
By the way...
Do you recognize this man?
No. Why?
Just following a lead, like I said.
Agent, I know you're under a lot
of pressure right now.
People want you to solve
this case yesterday.
- I know what that's like.
- I appreciate that.
So I don't want you to worry
that you've offended me
in any way.
- You don't, do you?
- No, if you say I haven't.
Well, that's a relief.
Now I really must be going.
Amanda, call me from the office.
There's some things
I need done before I land.
- We'll talk again, I'm sure.
- Mm.
Please, feel free to drop by anytime.
Lisbon, what gives?
This has gone on too long.
I need you to accept the fact
that you cannot break
Lorelei Martins out of prison.
Yes, I know that now.
Thank you. You were right.
You've come up with some plan
you don't want me to know about.
Well, that's an interesting theory.
I can see by your face
that Volker yielded nothing.
But you still like him
for the murder.
Yes, but he's tight
as a drum.
His assistant's looking
very promising.
I'm gonna go down there
and try to talk to her alone.
- You want me to come with you?
- Don't bother. I can manage.
You haven't really worked
on this case anyhow.
Okay.
- Uh, then... why are you here?
- Why are you here?
Repetition is the lowest form
of repartee.
Please, we can do
a little better than that.
Okay, Lisbon, I will
get on the case. I promise.
See you later.
Amanda, it's Agent Lisbon.
I need to speak to you.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
"Amanda, listen to me."
I know you think that Volker
killed Cassie Flood.
I think you're very afraid right now.
I can help you.
You can't say things like that.
That's not true.
You could get me in serious trouble.
Why, if it's not true?
Look, Volker was in San Francisco
at a charity event
with 300, 400 other people.
I was there with him.
He couldn't have killed
Cassie Flood.
I think we both know he wouldn't
have killed her himself.
No, I don't know that.
Amanda, if you keep silent
you are just as guilty as he is.
It's the same as if you
killed those people yourself...
not just Cassie Flood, but every
person in that Amazon village...
Women, children, babies.
You don't know what he's like.
What he's capable of.
Amanda, I promise nothing
is gonna happen to you
as long as you do the right thing.
I don't know.
You don't want this on your
conscience... any of it. You can't.
After the TV piece...
she came back, and she was
asking questions
about the geothermal project
and the massacred village.
And he told her that
the stories weren't true.
But I could see
that he was angry and lying.
That's all I know.
It's not enough to prove anything, is it?
No. No, but it helps.
Thank you, Amanda.
You are doing the right thing.
One last time.
Do you know who this man is?
No.
- Who is he?
- We're still trying to figure that out.
What will I do now?
Nothing. After we arrest Volker
you're gonna need to come in
and testify as to what you heard.
Until then, just keep quiet.
Carry on as normal.
Let us take care of everything.
I'm scared.
Do not worry.
When it's time for you
to speak, we'll protect you.
You have my word.
"Sounds like it's gonna be a hot one."
"You're not wrong there, Ed
but beautiful."
"Anybody out there who can"
"it'd be a great time to visit
the mountains or the beach."
"Not so easy if you're
a working man, Tara."
"Or a woman, Ed."
"Right."
Hello, Lisbon.
How do you do?
She cracked.
Volker's our man.
She doesn't have enough
to press charges on him.
We still need the actual killer.
Hmm. Funny you say that.
I just had an idea.
What kind of idea?
Come by the newsroom
tomorrow, and I'll show you.
Oh, and... and bring Cho.
- Good night.
- "Wait, what kind of idea?"
Jane...
Hello, Lisbon.
You at the newsroom?
- Yeah. Where are you?
- I'll be there in a minute.
I need to see an optometrist.
- What?
- I'll be with you soon.
- You're doing what?
- I'm going on the air.
Mr. Kasmir convinced me
that it's the right thing to do.
Ed, wind it up
and go to commercial.
"We'll be right back
after this."
Okay, but I'm gonna have to look
at the list of questions first.
No need to worry about that, Lisbon.
I've taken care of that already.
Ed, when we come back
from the commercial break
we'll go to an update on the progress
in the Cassidy Flood murder case.
"Okay. Is Mr. Jane here?"
Coming right in. Okay.
Come on.
- Showtime.
- Let's go get you prepped.
Give him some lipstick
and some blush.
Tara, did you move my glasses?
- Tara?
- No.
- Tara. Earth to Tara.
- Did you move my glasses?
- Nope. Nope.
Okay. All right. Okay.
I will lay out the progress of the case
thus far and then I'll go to you.
All right, Ed, and I'll bring it home
by telling you how we caught the killer.
- You caught the killer?
- Yeah.
Well, that's...
that's great. Who is it?
Wh... what... what was it
that, uh... that led you to him?
- It was all about the car in the end.
- The car?
News to me.
So we're just gonna
blow off the weather?
And we're live
in three, two, one.
"This is Ed Hunt"
with a special report
on the Cassie Flood murder case.
Patrick Jane is a consultant
with the California Bureau of Investigation.
- Hi, Ed.
- Mr. Jane.
You've got shocking new information
in the Cassie Flood murder.
- Is that right?
- Yes, I do, Ed.
Now, Cassie's car was tampered with
but earlier here at the station
we received a note that was connected
to a story of Cassie's
about the Bells Glen Speedway.
Are these things connected?
Well, that was an early
avenue of the investigation.
You're right there, Ed.
"But it turns out that's not
what I'm here to talk about."
Um...
- You're... you're not?
- No.
What the hell is he doing?
- Is he going off script?
- Yeah. He does that.
Uh, Tara, tell me
do you know Tommy Volker?
Uh, no.
- I... I mean, I know of him.
- Right.
Uh, Ed, you know
Tommy Volker, don't you?
Agent Jane, you were going to tell us
about the Bells Glen Speedway.
Cassie Flood told you she wanted to do
a story on Tommy Volker
and the massacred village
in the Amazon, right?
Ok... okay, let's, uh...
let's cut this.
This is great television.
Keep rolling until I say "stop."
Ed, you... you and Tommy are old
acquaintances, aren't you?
You do these adventures
together, like the...
The Dakar rally.
You're... you're adventurers.
- Right?
- Mr. Jane, um...
These are not the questions
we discussed.
The Dakar rally
is an endurance car race.
You and Mr. Volker must know
a lot about cars.
All right, we've... had enough.
Do you deny that you competed in
the Dakar rally with Mr. Volker?
- Of course not.
- And you don't deny having the, uh
necessary knowledge to tamper
with Cassie Flood's car?
- Yes!
- Yes.
No. No!
Do you deny that these
are your glasses?
Uh, well, they... they do...
- They look like mine.
- Mm. Uh-huh.
We found them in the wreckage
of Cassie's car.
Well, that's impossible.
I wasn't wearing them.
I...
I did not...
leave those in her car.
But you do admit to tampering
with Cassie Flood's car?
No.
"As God is my witness, no."
I think that counts
as an admission of guilt. Don't you?
Go get him, Cho.
"We'll be right back
after this short... commercial break."
I had no idea she'd be driving
on a road like that.
You've gotta believe that.
I only meant to scare her.
Just... to get her off the air.
That's why you sent the notes
to make her leave town?
I thought if she believed
Yuntz was out to get her, she'd...
leave the station, go someplace else
take somebody else's job.
- Not mine.
- Instead, you ended up killing her.
It wasn't my idea.
Volker...
- put me up to it.
- He had you tinker with her car?
We used to, uh, joke about
doing it during the Dakar...
uh, as a prank on somebody
you know.
So Volker told you to use it
to take care of Cassie.
It was more of a dare.
I couldn't back down
without looking like a coward.
A dare? That was enough to convince you
to murder Cassie Flood?
It wasn't supposed to be
a murder!
So you were manipulated
into committing a murder
beneficial to Tommy Volker.
And readily admit
that you have no evidence
that could implicate him
at all... is that about right?
This guy's a fool.
But this Volker seems formidable.
As smart and as careful
as I thought.
I don't know. How could
he be sure she'd be killed?
It looks like he just got lucky.
No, no. He always had
a plan "B."
The good Samaritan wasn't
just there to get the evidence.
He also made sure she was dead.
Volker's not gonna
get away with this.
I am gonna get him.
If not for the murder, then whatever
Amanda Shaw can give me.
Tax evasion, fraud
unpaid parking tickets.
I... I'm gonna bring in Amanda
and lean on her.
Look at you!
So tough.
I'm getting goosebumps.
It's been ten hours since anybody's heard
from Amanda Shaw.
We need a warrant to get
into her apartment right away.
Thanks, Judge.
Let's go.
Damn it.
Let's get her down from there.
She left a suicide note, you know?
Via e-mail.
Laying blame at your feet.
You will not get away
with this. I promise.
You have no idea what's
happening at all, do you?
Enjoy your job while you
still have it, Teresa.
- Agent "Lis-bon."
- It... it's Lisbon.
Lisbon. Pardon me.
Bob Kirkland
Homeland Security.
We don't know each other
but we need to talk.
- How can I help you, Mr. Kirkland?
- Call me Bob.
- Okay. What is it?
- Volker.
You need to stop worrying
about him, okay?
"Stop worrying about him."
What is that supposed to mean?
I'm telling you off the record
that it's being taken care of, trust me.
You should take a step back.
So you can take credit
for the arrest? Not a chance.
No. No, it's not like that.
But Volker is...
He's a very powerful man...
Agent.
Big contributor
to a lot of campaigns.
Is that supposed to scare me?
No.
You just need to watch your step.
Can I buy you
a cup of coffee sometime?
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Sorry, Mr. Jane.
- Oh, excuse me.
Do I know you?
No.
But I know you.